Hi everybody. Today is Saturday, October
11th, 2025 and our dear friend John Gri
who is back with us. Welcome back, John.
>> Thanks so much for having me, Nemo. It's
good to see you again.
>> John, I want to start with the case of
Charlie Kirk.
We can say today
almost everything every story they put
out so far is falling apart.
What is in your opinion when you look at
the case of Charlie Kirk? What is the
problem with the government? I I would
say with the security with intelligence
that how is that because this is a huge
bug. If you try to make his story and
you put it out, you know the text
messages between Charlie Kirk and his
partner, you know those text, you read
them, it's something like 1950s,
someone in those days talking, two
people are talking to each other. It's
it's so much you know unbelievably
can childish. Look at all these stories
coming out and falling apart mean
debunked by the podcasters, you know, by
the analysts
like Larry Johnson that we have it on.
We have him on every every week and he
said that it's not possible being shot
but that particular rifle at that
distance and the bullet just stucking in
the neck of Charlie Kirk not getting out
from the other side. What is your take
on what has happened during this
assassination and in the aftermath
specifically in the aftermath in the
aftermath of the assassination of
Charlie Kirk and the stories that
they're trying to convince the public
opinion with them.
>> First Nema I want to preface it my
response by saying that I am not a
conspiracy theorist. I am the least
conspiratorial
of anybody I know. I generally think
conspiracy theories are just stories
that people come up with to fill gaps
that they either investigatively or
intellectually can't can't uh cover.
With that said, I think Larry Johnson's
right. We're not getting the story here.
Uh let's look at the gun. The gun was a
30 odd six, right?
older gun, iron uh sights, not a scope,
iron sights.
Is it possible for the kid that's been
accused of killing Charlie Kirk to make
that shot? It's possible,
but with a 30 odd six, there's no
possible way it's going to lodge lodge
in the neck. It should have blown the
the left half of his head off by going
through the neck, coming out the
backside and taking out everything that
it hit. But it didn't.
Um, another issue is is the escape.
First of all, how how is it even
possible that he was able to get up onto
the roof of the uh the closed being
renovated student center
uh undetected. I find that hard to
believe. But while carrying a 30 odd six
rifle,
we heard a lot after the the killing
that he took it apart quickly. Now we
know that he didn't take it apart. It
was found intact in the woods. So then
what? He shot Charlie Kirk and then
somehow miraculously got off the roof of
the building and had nobody see him
carrying a rifle as he was running away.
There are so many questions here that
the government isn't answering, that the
authorities aren't answering, that of
course people are going to come up with
with different ideas and different
scenarios. But another question I have
that I think we haven't really asked
ourselves yet is why is the FBI involved
in the first place. Okay, this this
killing was was in Utah, right? The
shooter was from Utah.
He alleged shooter. He left his home in
Utah and drove to the site of the crime
which was in Utah.
There was no crossing of state lines.
There was literally nothing to
federalize this case. So why in the
world did the FBI run to Utah to take
over the case? It's not a federal case.
And it just makes me think that there's
some sort of cover up of foot here.
And like you said, and you said
correctly,
every time we're presented with
with a plausibility,
it falls apart under scrutiny. And
listen, if if podcasters like me, like I
can poke holes in the state and the
FBI's investigation,
then they should be ashamed of
themselves.
Then we know that the official story is
not what really happened.
John
I think anything happens in my opinion
one of the basic reasons for any
engineer for anyone who has learned
mathematic would say quib bono who's
going to benefit from that
>> who's because you know even we if we
assume that something internal has
happened in the United States why did
the authorities I'm talking about Donald
Trump himself and his vice
JD Vance he did they didn't come out and
saying something to bring all the people
from all the sections factions of the
society together their argument Donald
Trump first comment on the assassination
he was the far left it's the you know
the radicals they're doing this and Net
came out these are is Islamists doing
this
how can you understand that how can you
imagine ing that
it seems we have some sort of issue with
John's connection. He's in Mexico and he
has a weak connection. Yeah, he he came
back.
>> Yeah, sorry about that.
>> Um, yeah, I I heard your uh I heard your
question and and it's a good one. Why
why didn't uh the White House try to
bring people together and Quibono? Let's
look at Quibono first.
Who benefits? There are a lot of
different factions that benefit,
frankly. On the one hand, um, as crazy
as it might sound, Charlie Kirk's
murder,
John, we don't hear you.
John, can you hear me?
Yeah, the same sort of problem.
Yeah, so sorry for that. But this is a
problem with the internet connection
that John has right now. But he's gonna
be back and
we have to deal with that for the time
being. Yeah.
>> I apologize, Neiman, and I apologize to
your viewers. I'm in I'm in very rural
Mexico on the southern tip of the Baja
Peninsula and there's just no
connectivity down here. Anyway, getting
back to your point,
>> Quibono,
>> so both people and and groups on both
the right and the left benefit from
this. On the one hand, the right gets a
martyr to the point where there have
been congressional bills sponsored just
in the past several weeks to make a
Charlie Kirk coin commemorative coin but
in the National Mint uh to there was a a
bill this week that this past week that
was sponsored to build um a Charlie Kirk
memorial statue on on the campus of
every state university in America. It's
it's insanity.
Uh on the other hand,
a silent charlie Kirk benefits the left
because Charlie Kirk was was
bringing a lot of people, a lot of young
people into con the conservative
movement and the Republican party. And
if you're a Democratic party that
doesn't really have a program or a
policy or strategy, then that's a very
dangerous thing.
I I I want to believe
that it's not possible for somebody in
my government to be so evil as to
assassinate a pri a private citizen or
any citizen
uh for the purpose of squaltching
political debate. But I mean, we've
we've seen what's happened in the United
States over the years. Of course, there
are people that are willing to do that.
I I just hope that it's not I hope we're
wrong about this, Nema. I hope that
there was not a conspiracy. I hope that
everything is finally explained and that
it was this kid, this Tyler Johnson, I
think his name was, whatever whatever
his name is. I hate to even honor him by
using his name. Um
>> but
Robinson.
>> Yeah, that's right.
John,
what is I think many people who are
arguing
right now I'm reading the comments here.
They're talking about the MSAD, Israel
being behind this, but curious what is
the reason that people go in that
direction because they see that Israel
is in a desperate situation in terms of
the public opinion in the United States
and Charlie Kirk was one of the main
important characters even with the
election with the Trump's presidency. He
helped a lot during the Yeah, that's why
they they feel that if Charlie K has
decided to leave Israel and pro-Israel
cause that could be a reason for Israel
to go after him, you know, and there
were many issues with that. We we I had
Max Blumenthal on this show and he
mentioned each and every detail and
these people who are supporters of
Israel
and they did everything to make them
suspicious about what has happened
during the assassination. What is your
understanding? What is behind this sort
of feeling on the part of the people and
maybe broader issue with the case of
Israel?
Yeah, Max Blumenthal is a friend of mine
and I'll tell you what, he's one of the
most brilliant people I've ever
encountered. He is able to put these
pieces of a puzzle together in a way
that almost no one else I know is able
to do. Charlie Kirk
throughout his life was one of the most
pro-Israel,
one of the most pro-Zionism
figures uh on the American right
until recently.
Even Charlie Kirk
began to take a stand against Israeli
war crimes in in Gaza. You know, at the
same time, there was a poll that was
released this last week, Nemo. I'm sure
that you saw it and I think it's very
important. On October 7th, 2023,
[Music]
Americans supported Israel over the
Palestinians by 46
percentage points. This week, Americans
support the Palestinians by one
percentage point over the Israelis. So,
the Israelis are losing American public
opinion and they're doing it very
quickly. Well, if somebody as powerful,
as respected as Charlie Kirk with a
following the size of Charlie Kirks,
decides to switch sides and support the
Palestinian cause or Palestinian human
rights, just human rights. That would be
a serious problem for the Israelis. So,
did the Israelis have have a reason for
this to happen? You bet they did. Did
they do it? I don't see it. But
yeah, the same issue. He's going to come
up. So sorry for that that it it
happens. I can do nothing about it and
we have to wait and he's going to join
us in in a second. Yeah, he's here.
>> Sorry, man.
>> No, no problem. I tell you what, there's
no hot water. There's no internet. There
are bugs everywhere. I spend an hour
just killing all the bugs that come into
my room that one day to the next. It's
tough gig.
>> Yeah.
When you look at the case of Charlie
Kirk, do you think that
the Republican party would be able to
replace him? I'm I'm talking let's put
it out let's let's put it out this way.
I'm not talking about the Republican by
the MAGA. Is he replaceable
>> and with someone who would support
Israel instead of what Charlie Kirk said
because we've learned from the messages
he you know he he had with his friends
before the assassination 48 hours before
the assassination he said that I'm done
with Israel. I'm not going to support
them anymore because of what has
happened internally. You know those
people donors of the movement they have
decided $2 billion they have decided to
withdraw
their support for the movement TPUSA
turning point USA and
right after the assassination we've we
we saw how Ben Shapiro came out and said
I'm going to put out this you know
amount of money to support you.
How is that mo movement today in your
opinion? Are they going to be able to
continue the movement even without
Charlie Kirk, which in my opinion was
the center of the movement?
>> Yeah, Charlie Kirk was the center of the
movement. I agree. Um, you know, they
have Ben Shapiro, they have Benny
Johnson, they have a handful of other
people. They're not Charlie Kirk. So,
this is going to hurt. This is going to
do damage. Donald Trump said that he
would not have been elected to a second
term were it not for Char Charlie Kirk.
It was Charlie Kirk that brought young
people voting for the very first time
over not just to the Trump campaign but
to MAGA as a movement.
And so Charlie Kirk was one of those
unique figures who who had a
generational impact on American
politics. Think of somebody like Martin
Luther King or Robert F. Kennedy Senior.
I I would compare his political power,
his authority to those people. You know,
I met him one time.
He was a kid. He was 17 or 18 years old.
Uh, I was working on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee and he came with a
group of Tea Party people, which was
funny to me because I was watching them
momentarily and I thought, you know
what? It's that kid who's the leader.
It's not any of the adults. This kid is
the leader. And then they were going
office to office lobbying for for tax
cuts. And then um
and then when it came time to leave,
there was a press conference and he did
the press conference, a 17-year-old kid.
And I remember saying to a colleague of
mine, "Boy, that that kid's going
places, whoever he is." Like, who is he?
Oh, his name's Charlie Kirk. I said, "I
never heard of him. He's just a child."
And he was leading a movement at the age
of 17. That's why I I say that he was
one of those whether you like him or
not, whether you agree with him or not,
and I found myself disagreeing with him
on I don't know 80% of the issues, he
was a born leader, and that was that was
what his real service to the right and
to the Republican party was.
John, when it comes to the establishment
of the United States, I really don't
believe that the establishment is, you
know, political. They're ideological
and, you know, they don't belong to the
right and left and all these movements
that we see in the United States. But in
the case of Charlie Kirk, do you think
that
[Music]
how how what is your understanding of
the policies of the establishment when
something like Charlie Kirk happens, the
the assassination of this guy? Because
this is not something new for the United
States. We had JFK, his brother, and we
have many many cases. You you better you
know better than anyone else. But these
are huge these sort of assassinations
make huge unrest within the society.
And how what is your understanding of
the establishment in these sort of
moments that they have to are they you
know how much they
somehow involved in this sort of you
know
I I don't know if you understand what
what I want to ask you. I think the
establishment has a big has a a
you know has a problem with what's going
on in the United States. The
establishment doesn't have the leverage
that they had before because of Israel,
because of the war in Ukraine, because
of what's going on internally in the
United States, because of Charlie Kirk
himself, you know,
>> how do they want to solve their problem
to resolve their problems?
Yeah, that's a very good question and
it's a very very difficult one to
answer. First of all, you're correct.
Um, it's it's all about ideology.
There are more Americans who call
themselves independents than there are
Democrats or Republicans. People ask me
what political party I'm a member of. I
am an independent independent truly
but I'm I was a third generation
Democrat.
My grandparents came because of Franklin
Roosevelt. Uh
Democrats, you know, through the the
Vietnam War. My parents were opposed to
the war. They were supportive of civil
rights.
I left the Democratic party.
Sorry about this connectivity. It's it
it wants to work so much and it just
doesn't seem to have the strength to do
it.
>> So,
we've gotten to a point in the country
where ideology is more important than
than party politics. And it's making the
parties crazy.
They want so much to be able to make
this a a two-party system again. Uh but
they don't know how to do it. And they
don't know how to do it because they're
unwilling to address the issues, the
kinds of issues that Charlie Kirk was
raising. For example,
point two is whether we like to admit it
to ourselves or not, we have a very very
violent society.
I I served in Bahrain for two years. Two
of the happiest years of my life. And
the Amir of Bahrain at the time, Sheikh
uh Isa bin Salman al- Khalifa was a very
kind and generous man. He used to open
up his beach house on the weekends for
diplomats to go swim and your wives
could wear a bikini and nobody would
stare at them. And the Amir would always
invite us over to have tea
and
time right after the Oklahoma City
bombing got that attack.
So the conventional wisdom was that some
kind of Mus that it's not a Muslim who
did this. And I said, "Oh, your
highness, I say the same thing every
day. It would be so bad for us, for all
of us." And he said, "You know the thing
about you Americans, you have an
unusually violent society. even by Arab
standards. He said, "You are accepting
of violence that would be unacceptable
in any other civilized country." And I
didn't know how to respond to that
because he was right.
You know, oh, you don't like Charlie
Kirk's uh uh talks, shoot him in the
neck. You don't like uh Capitol Hill
politics? Go to the Congressional
Softball game and shoot as many members
of Congress as you can. You want to make
a political point about gun control, go
into a school and open fire on children
because the law is not going to change.
Nobody's going to stop you. Nobody's
going to ban guns. Nobody's going to
make mandatory registration. Nobody's
going to do anything.
So, I think that the reason why people
are falling away from the political
parties is because the political parties
don't affect change in any way. The
American people really do want change.
The parties aren't willing to do it. The
parties are essentially two sides of the
same coin. A lot of people disagree with
me, Nemo, when I say this, but you know,
I worked on Capitol Hill for years. I
worked in the CIA for 15 years. Um, I
served overseas for my country. I I've
come to realize
that there's really no major difference
between the two political parties. You
can you can tell that there are little
differences around the edge, you know,
maybe a little bit about abortion, maybe
a little bit about the economy or taxes,
but essentially these two parties are
the same party, two sides of the same
coin. And people are coming to realize
that and they're tired of it.
>> Yeah. Actually, what's happening right
now?
You see Marjgerie Taylor Green going
with Democrats? It's unbelievable.
>> A friend of mine tweeted yesterday, who
she tweeted at Marjgerie Taylor Green
and she said, "Who are you and what have
you done with Marjorie Taylor Green?"
I said to I said to a friend of mine
just two days ago, I can't believe that
I wake up in the morning, read the news,
and agree with everything that Marjgerie
Taylor Green is saying. What kind of
crazy country have we become? I don't
understand it.
>> Yeah. Actually, she called what has
happened in Gaza, she called it genocide
before Bernie Sanders. you you know it's
huge for those people who are
criticizing the policies in in the
Middle East in Palestine.
>> Yeah, I I'm smiling because it's so
ridiculous, but then at the same time
it's also a clear indication of the
current state of American politics.
Listen, on my own podcast, my my old
radio show, I used to make fun of
Marjorie Taylor Green mercilessly.
Mercilessly.
But man, it's like every time she opens
her mouth these days, she's right. And I
find myself agreeing with her.
>> It's just it's not just about her. It's
about Tucker Carlson, Candace Owen.
>> That's right.
>> In my opinion, you look at, you know,
Steve Bannon talking about if if you
want to go if you want to expand the war
in the Middle East, you Israel, you
better go. you by yourself, we're not
going to be there to help you anymore.
We're not gonna
>> and I think Donald Trump is
understanding. Do you think that one of
the main reasons that maybe I I don't
know if
because we can be pessimist about what's
going on with the peace deal between the
United States and Israelis on one side
and Hamas and Middle Eastern countries
on the other hand. But after all,
do you think that if the deal is for
real and Donald Trump wants to do
something about it, is it because of the
political pressure within the party
within the base of MAGA?
>> Yeah, I believe that's exactly what it
is. Donald Trump has no love of
Palestinians. He has no love of Islam or
or of Arabs in general. Um but if if he
really is the face of MAGA, MAGA is
against foreign wars. It's against US
intervention in foreign wars. And we're
in this war up to our necks. Also,
Donald Trump is obsessed with winning
the Nobel Peace Prize. And if he can if
he can bring peace even indirectly
to Gaza
with a deal that's acceptable to the
Gazins,
you know, maybe that gives him a chance
at the Nobel Peace Prize. Um, a couple
of other things, too.
[Music]
Where do I even begin? Yeah,
>> Donald Trump
Donald Trump can can go down in history
as one of two things. He can go down in
history as just like Richard Nixon did
when he went to China as this
cuttingedge
leader in foreign policy. Or he can go
down as Grover Cleveland, who was
president in the late 19th century,
served two non-consecutive terms, and
nobody remembers who in the world he is.
He wants to be the former. He wants to
be that historic
president who finally brought peace to
the Middle East. I don't know if that's
going to be the case or not.
Um, another thing though too is is Iran.
Iran plays a major role in this
conversation.
And I'm probably crazy for saying it.
I've said it a couple of times, but I'll
say it again. Just like Nixon was the
only president who could go to China and
finally make peace with the Chinese in
1972,
maybe Trump is the only one who can go
to Iran. And I don't mean literally
physically go to Iran, but maybe go to
Riad.
and at the invitation of Muhammad bin
Salman meet with President Peshki.
Stranger things have happened through
history but maybe now is when we can
make a deal. And I want to make one
other point. I think this is an
important one.
Benjamin Netanyahu went too far when he
bombed Qatar.
Too far.
The Qataris are not just an ally of the
United States. They are a major non-NATO
ally. They have the same status as
Bahrain, as Japan, as South Korea, as
Australia, and we are compelled to
protect them. Not just because they're
major non-NATO allies, but because Qatar
is the home of the world's largest air
force base and it belongs to us.
And so I can imagine
that conversation between the Amir and
President Trump saying, "What's wrong
with you? We're friends. We're allies.
We gave you this gigantic air base. We
have great relations. We're friends. We
just gave you a Boeing 747 for your own
use and you allow the Israelis to bomb
us."
And so Trump had to go public and say
the Israelis,
you know, didn't give me enough time to
warn the Gutis that was probably not
true. And then when he was embarrassed
after Netanyahu came out and said, "Oh,
sure. I gave I gave Donald Trump two
hours notice before I bombed Cutter,"
Trump realized that this could ruin
everything.
And I think that finally he came to the
re realization that Israel acts in the
national interests of Israel
and the US must act in the national
interests of the United States.
>> There is nothing else that Donald Trump
and the United States can do for Israel.
I don't know how we've learned that the
United States has spent since October
2023 they have spent more than $32
billion for the case of for Israel you
know inside Israel sending weapons going
to fight Yemenes you know the region
>> and what has happened what was the
outcome for Israel today what is Israel
today are they because before just
imagine what it was in the mind of the
people in the Middle East. I'm talking
about the Middle Eastern sort of view
toward Israel. They thought that Israel
is hugely you know the they their
military is the technology of their
military is above all and they cannot
nobody in the Middle East can fight them
and they thought that Israel cannot be
defeated and Israel has you know looking
at what Israel has done to Gaza. Yeah.
Yeah. They destroyed everything. They
committed genocide. That would be the
legacy of Israel.
>> Yes.
>> You know, forever.
>> I don't know how they can change that is
not possible.
>> No.
>> Can we do something about Holocaust? And
is it's not possible to to remove it
from the history.
>> No. It's done. They've they've done it.
They've done it.
>> They don't understand the gravity of
what's going on with all these issues.
Yeah, that's exactly right. They've
they've carried out this genocide. It's
it's in the history books now. And uh
that you can't go back and take it back.
You know, it's not an accident that all
of these European countries plus Canada
plus Australia um have recently
recognized Palestine. They've done it
because of the of the genocide,
right? They've done it to put pressure
on the Israelis. and the Israelis can't
just pretend that it hasn't happened.
Another thing too that I think we should
all be afraid of, I think that the
leadership of of the Israeli government,
not just Netanyahu, but the likes of
Smootrich and Bengavir and and these
other right-wing extremists, extremists
who have been convicted of of anti- Arab
and anti-Muslim hate crimes, felonies,
and who now lead the Israeli government.
I think that they are crazy enough to
use nuclear weapons.
And so I think that should be our next
great fear. By some accounts, the
Israelis have between 200 and 220
million um forgive me 200 and 220
um nuclear warheads. I think we should
believe them when they say that there's
no way that they'll lose a war. I think
that we should believe them when they
threaten Iran with nuclear war. And so
the only thing that's going to keep them
from doing that is pressure, real
pressure from the United States. I'm
glad to see Donald Trump pressuring
Israel right now, but I don't know if
this is a one day or one week, you know,
event
or if this is going to be US policy. I
want to add too, Nema, that I am
colossally disappointed in the
leadership of the Democratic Party.
Some of them talk a good game. Most of
them remain silent in the face of of
this genocide in Gaza. But then when
Netanyahu comes to the United States,
they literally run.
There are films of them running to the
room where Netanyahu was appearing so
they could take a picture with him. It
makes me sick to my stomach to think of
it. Another thing, too, and I think
we're having an impact. Forgive me for
personalizing this, but I think this is
important.
Um, I was mentioned in a in a
publication this past week that I've
never heard of before called the Middle
East Forum.
I was criticized by the political
adviser to the Israeli foreign minister.
He called me virulently anti-semitic.
That first of all, that's one of the
most ridiculous things anybody has ever
said about me. It's it's just comical.
Virulently anti-semitic. Okay. Anybody
who doesn't tow the Israeli line 100% is
an anti-semite. I get that that's the
Israeli uh script right now. But he said
that my position on Israel
shows the rot
that is taking hold in the intellectual
class of the American left.
I took that to be a compliment
because to me that means people on the
American political left, which is really
a centrist position, uh people on the
American left are finally coming around
and seeing with open eyes what it is
that the Israelis are doing to helpless
Palestinians.
You you destroy the entire Gaza Strip.
You destroy every hospital. You destroy
the electrical grid. You destroy the
water treatment facilities. You kill
70,000, 100,000,
150,000 people, most of whom are women
and children, almost all of whom are
civilians. And you're proud of that?
So, I'm proud at least to be a part of
the rotting
American intellectual left. I'm going to
wear that as a badge of honor.
Yeah,
we know one of the main issues, one of
the main issue for the Iranians during
the first phase of the conflict between
the two Iran and Israel was the as we
talked about it before the counter
intelligence on the part of Iranian
being so weak and you know they had a
huge network of spies in Iran.
>> Huge huge bigger than anybody suspected.
Yeah. Once something that big happens to
a country, John, and they go after, you
know, cleaning all these, you know,
finding these people and, you know, do
you think that Israel with that attack
has just destroyed the the network they
had in Iran or
how big if they have something on in
Iran as we talk today, how big That
would be that the government in Iran can
is not able to find them just to
>> Yeah, sorry. I heard your question.
>> So, um
kudos first to the Israelis for this
this counter inelligence
um network that they had in Iran. it by
all accounts it was thousands literally
thousands of people reporting
clandestinely back to the Mossad. Uh we
know now this is what the Iranian
government has turned up that many of
these people thousands of people were
Afghan refugees
uh who were in uh in Iran um illegally
or didn't have documentation and uh you
know were probably offered the
equivalent of you know $50 a month or
$100 a month money well spent to just
tell the Israelis where the nuclear
scientists lived, where the generals
lived, what time the generals left their
apartment buildings in the morning to go
to work of I mean all these little it's
called the mosaic concept where you have
just a little tile a little piece of
information but then you put it all
together at Mossad headquarters and you
come up with an entire picture
and that's what made Israeli targeting
so much easier. The Iranians have broken
up a lot of this. There have been some
executions. There have been uh a handful
of trials. There there have been
imprisonments, but I would have to think
that it's impossible to get all of them.
That there are still people reporting
back to the Israelis besides those those
Israeli Mossad officers who are ethnic
Persians and who speak Farsy without an
accent and who are able to blend into
Iranian society.
This is going to be a very very
difficult uh thing for the Iranian
government to to dig these dig these
spies up and uh and root them out. Uh
but it's also something that the
Israelis have been working on for years.
This isn't something that that you
implement overnight. It's a program that
takes years to develop. And um and
another thing too, this something that I
think the Iranians should should um
think about
Uh the the Afghan refugees who were
recruited by Mossad were not recruited
by long-distance telephone call from
Israel to Iran. They were recruited in
person.
There are people inside Iran today
acting as spy masters and running these
networks. And I guarantee you that the
networks are compartmentalized. They are
stovepiped. So, one network doesn't know
what the other network is doing. One
network doesn't know what the other
network's uh orders or instructions are.
Why? Because if one network is
discovered and everybody is rounded up
and arrested,
they'll never tell what the other
network is doing because they don't have
any idea just in case they needed to
fight against the Iranians and it worked
out. The only thing that stopped the
Israelis I think was if you listen to
Donald Trump uh was because
uh the US bombed uh bombed Iran on
Israel's behalf. Donald Trump said that
Benjamin Netanyahu said that if the
United States didn't bomb the Iranian
nuclear sites that the Israelis would
use a nuclear a tactical nuclear weapon
because they didn't have um a
conventional weapon big enough powerful
enough to destroy a deep underground
site. But imagine if they had used a
nuclear weapon that would change the
world. The whole world would change if a
nuclear weapon were to be deployed
against Iran.
And so the the Iranians have um
a lot of work to do when it comes to
trying to disrupt and dismantle this
what appears to be an enormous Israeli
intelligence operation on Iranian soil.
We're not talking just about recruiting
the random Iran nuclear scientist who
goes to Europe for some seminar. We're
talking about giant networks on the
ground all across Iran.
>> Yeah.
>> John, to wrap up this session, do you
feel that Israel would attack Iran?
>> What's your take on that?
>> If Israel wants to attack Iran and what
would be because after all, we have to
see if we want to answer this question
in my opinion. You I want to hear your
take as well. But
what would be the outcome for Israel if
they attack Iran for the second time?
>> Yeah.
Yeah. The same problem. He's going to be
back just in a minute. In a sec. 10
seconds.
Yeah,
>> my my apologies, man. Just as I opened
my mouth to answer the question, it it
cut off. Um, the Iranians have exercised
something that that everybody's calling
strategic patience. Uh, honest to God,
when when the Israelis first began
attacking Iran,
I think the whole world was surprised at
how patient the Iranian government
took its response to the point where the
Iranian people were in the streets
demanding that the government respond. I
think the Iranian government
Yeah, the same problem.
He's going to come up.
>> Sorry. I think that the Iranian
government um
did everything right in the way it
responded to these Israeli attacks. But
the conventional wisdom and I think this
is probably correct. I'm sorry to say if
you listen to Tita Parsy or Max
Blumenthal or Larry Johnson or any
number of of
people who know these things, I would
expect Israel to attack again.
I think that we'll we're going to start
seeing propaganda coming from uh the
Israelis saying that the Iranians have
already restarted their uh their nuclear
program or they've begun rebuilding
their nuclear sites or they're taking a
shipment of uh you know gyroscopes or
whatever. I I think I think we should
expect to see something like that. I
think that there will be another um
Israeli attack and I think that the
Iranians probably either will not strike
back or will will do something symbolic
like like drones again.
And I think that is really the way to
go. Now, with that said,
I don't blame the Iranians for wanting
to build a nuclear weapons program. They
have to protect themselves. And if
they're going to be constantly attacked
by Israel, constantly bombed by Israel,
then they're going to have to create a
deterrent that is big enough, that is
strong enough to really deter the
Israelis.
And you know, maybe they don't have to
start from scratch. Maybe they get help
from the Pakistanis or from the North
Koreans.
Who knows? But uh I I do expect another
attack on on Iran. I just hope that the
Iranians continue to be as patient as
they have been so far.
>> No,
>> thank you so much, John, for being with
us today. I know that we had some
difficulties because of the connect. It
wasn't your fault. It was the
connection. Yeah. Thank you so much.
>> Thank you. Thank you. Great to see you
again.
>> Yeah. See you soon.
>> Have a great time, Jo.
>> Thank you so much.